MUHAMAD RIBIN

WEB DEVELOPER



V. -

+91 8943915070



muhdribin@gmail.com



Malappuram,Kerala,India



https://github.com/RIBINZX

PROFILE

As a Python full-stack developer, I have extensive experience developing and deploying full-stack web applications using Python frameworks such as Django. I have strong skills in front-end development technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Django
- Python
- Rest API
- Front-Back End Developer
- Problem-Solving
- HTML/CSS/JS
- SQL

EXPERIENCE

GEDEXO DESIGN AND TECHNOLOGY

Role: Website Developer and Designer

2023 - Present

- Developed and designed e-commerce sites for clients
- Collaborated with clients and team members to ensure project goals were met
- Provided website maintenance and support to clients

OXDU TECH

Role: Website Developer and Designer

2022 - 2023

- website developer and website design
- Developed and designed e-commerce websites
- Educational institutions

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Elayur, Malappuram

2020 - 2022